<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vintage on Hugo Hacker Theme</title>
    <link>/categories/vintage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vintage on Hugo Hacker Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/categories/vintage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CAPSTER CONVENIENT WAY TO EXECUTE THINGS ON WINDOWS 7 STARTUP</title>
      <link>/news/capster-convenient-way-to-execute-things-on-windows-7-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/capster-convenient-way-to-execute-things-on-windows-7-startup/</guid>
      <description>Although I have been using Linux more and more in recent work, Windows 7 remains my main production operating system. And here is an excellent finding for Windows 7 crony named [Capster]. Its main functionality is to launch the specified executable at startup time when the [CAPS LOCK] key is set to ON or OFF. I use Capser to run backup script, that backs up previously selected folders [if i want to].</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO COPY FILES FROM ANDROID PHONE TO PC IN AN EASY AND FAST WAY</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-copy-files-from-android-phone-to-pc-in-an-easy-and-fast-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-copy-files-from-android-phone-to-pc-in-an-easy-and-fast-way/</guid>
      <description>First things first. I often need to copy substantial amount of photos from my phone. It can&amp;rsquo;t be done via Windows GUI without millions of mouse clicks or keystrokes. Here you will find a solution on how to do this in a proper way. The key tool for this will be [ADB], developer tools for Android.&#xA;Wishes: command line, batch, no file explorer, no mouse, no clickety-clack.&#xA;Sicking tired of all of these not-so-precise-instructions i&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make my own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO SETUP CUSTOM FONTS IN WINDOWS 7 CONSOLE</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-setup-custom-fonts-in-windows-7-console/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-setup-custom-fonts-in-windows-7-console/</guid>
      <description>As a hardcore user of [dual-panel orthodox file manager] i always suffered because of sucky look of default console fonts. Native preloaded font list has quite scarce selection, if you ask me. To fix such disappointment you&amp;rsquo;ll need:&#xA;install desired fonts by means of windows control panel copy EXACT FONT NAME fonts section in control panel paste it into registry key into following branch HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SOFTWARE\Microsoft\Windows NT\CurrentVersion\Console\TrueTypeFont note that every new subsequent font should be added by a key with added one zero to registry key name reboot computer to apply &amp;amp; enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO ENABLE SVG PREVIEW IN WINDOWS EXPLORER ON WINDOWS 7</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-enable-svg-preview-in-windows-explorer-on-windows-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-enable-svg-preview-in-windows-explorer-on-windows-7/</guid>
      <description>So, you want to be a hip and would like to have the feature of SVG preview in file explorer like in fancy windows 11 of friend of yours? It is surely possible, even on such old crone like Windows 7!&#xA;[SVG See] is an excellent application, which bring such functionality to our crony operating system.&#xA;If you are for some reason don&amp;rsquo;t observe SVG previews in explorer there are a couple of things that you could try to fix things up:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUBBA HO-TEP [2002] ▀ HIDDEN MOVIE WITH BRUCE CAMPBELL</title>
      <link>/news/bubba-ho-tep-2002-hidden-movie-with-bruce-campbell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/bubba-ho-tep-2002-hidden-movie-with-bruce-campbell/</guid>
      <description>&#xA;[Bubba Ho-Tep] is a quite awkward movie, but despite that is worth watching. The main reasons of such conclusion are [Bruce Campbell] and [Brian Tyler]. Bruce is surely known for his [Evil Dead] acting. Brian provided stunning soundtrack, which lifts whole movie to another level.&#xA;OFFICIAL TRAILER&#xA;Imagery by spacedrone808 @Adobe Imagery by spacedrone808 @Freepik </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO FIX OUT OF SYNC TIME ON OLD WINDOWS 7 INSTALLATIONS</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-fix-out-of-sync-time-on-old-windows-7-installations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-fix-out-of-sync-time-on-old-windows-7-installations/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago i run into problem related to out-of sync time clock. Tried almost all imaginable solutions, like time service restarting, checking that internet time-sync option is turned on and so on and so forth. Of course to no avail at all. How typical! My Windows 7 installation dates back to early 2019 and i&amp;rsquo;ve plethora of software installed, and more over system is heavily customized so plain reinstall of operating system is not an option in my case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO EASILY FIX GPS ISSUES ON SONY XZ1 COMPACT SMARTPHONE</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-easily-fix-gps-issues-on-sony-xz1-compact-smartphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-easily-fix-gps-issues-on-sony-xz1-compact-smartphone/</guid>
      <description>As you may know [Sony Xperia XZ1 Compact] is my main web surfing phone on the go. I&amp;rsquo;m fully satisfied with it&amp;rsquo;s capabilities even in 2023. Except one little problem, related to GPS and speed of satellites detection.&#xA;Issue showed up couple of months ago and it seems that i finally found an easy way to fix it. After some investigations i conclude that device has a hardware based problem, and to eliminate it completely you need to open phone casing and pull up antenna so it will have tighter surface touching with in-case metallic plate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVEN MORE CLASSICAL TRACKER MUSIC</title>
      <link>/news/even-more-classical-tracker-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/even-more-classical-tracker-music/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED ON: 2023-08-19&#xA;For those of you who are hunger for more classical tracker music and you are not completely satisfied with my [ultimate tracker mod collection] here is a link to a [marvelous catalog] of chiptune and demoscene gems. Design matches aesthetics of early 90s and pleasing to eye.&#xA;Resource is kindly provided by [Matt].&#xA;Oh, and here is a massive breakdown of tracker music resources i&amp;rsquo;ve stashed for you:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO STAY SAFE WHEN USING OB-SOUL-EEE-TEE WINDOWS 7 IN 2023?</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-stay-safe-when-using-ob-soul-eee-tee-windows-7-in-2023-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-stay-safe-when-using-ob-soul-eee-tee-windows-7-in-2023-/</guid>
      <description>I often get asked regarding Windows 7 safety especially in 2023.&#xA;&amp;#34;Is it safe to use such old operating system?&amp;#34; &amp;#34;What about security?&amp;#34; &amp;#34;How about modern viruses?&amp;#34;&#xD;.... &amp;hellip;. and many other similar questions.&#xA;Funny thing that people who are asking about security don&amp;rsquo;t give a damn about privacy. Yeah, that&amp;rsquo;s quite different definitions for sure, but from my point of view they always come together hand in hand.&#xA;The main and the most important security police officer is your head.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO MINIMIZE LAPTOP POWER CONSUMPTION</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-minimize-laptop-power-consumption/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-minimize-laptop-power-consumption/</guid>
      <description>Say you need to run on a laptop battery vintage or simply non-demanding applications for an extremely long time. Here is a little breakdown of mandatory things to do:&#xA;turn off in BIOS unneeded devices like camera, sd-card reader, fingerprint scanner, gsm-modem, wifi, bt or whatever you are not using turn on power saving features like various C-power states turn off hyper-threading and hi-core count [if you have such ability] lower screen brightness to acceptable level check my [quick] and [comprehensive] optimization FAQs get rid of [unneeded services and bloat applications] Also you can use core parking utility [Park Control], but in this mini-guide i&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to set power related things up via internal Windows 7 tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO SET PROPER COLOR FOR CURSOR AND COMMENTS IN VSCODE EDITOR</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-set-proper-cursor-color-in-vscode/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-set-proper-cursor-color-in-vscode/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED ON: 2023-12-02&#xA;The main reason i&amp;rsquo;ve decided to write this note is indistinct default color mappings and inability to solve issue simply using GUI of software.&#xA;In main configuration file:&#xA;settings.json add following lines:&#xA;&amp;#34;workbench.colorCustomizations&amp;#34;: {&#xD;&amp;#34;editorCursor.foreground&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;#ff0000&amp;#34;,&#xD;&amp;#34;terminalCursor.foreground&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;#02ED3D&amp;#34;,&#xD;&amp;#34;editorLineNumber.activeForeground&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;#ff0000&amp;#34;,&#xD;&amp;#34;editor.lineHighlightBackground&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;#016119&amp;#34;,&#xD;&amp;#34;editor.lineHighlightBorder&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;#02ED3D&amp;#34;,&#xD;&amp;#34;terminal.foreground&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;#02ed3d&amp;#34; }, To set custom color for GREY comments drop in these lines:&#xA;&amp;#34;editor.tokenColorCustomizations&amp;#34;: {&#xD;&amp;#34;conmments&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;#ff006f&amp;#34;&#xD;} To fast access configuration file press:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO RUN LATEST VS CODE IN WINDOWS 7 X64</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-run-latest-vs-code-in-windows-7-x64/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-run-latest-vs-code-in-windows-7-x64/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED ON: 2024-07-05 v1.81.1 is a more recent version, which can be executed without any efforts v1.89 is a hacked [FINAL version] for Windows 7 x64 So, Windows 7 users are pretty safe at this point despite artificial restrictions of big corps.&#xA;Usually i&amp;rsquo;m not feeling so delightful regarding microsoft modern programs, but this one is pretty good. And of course they tried to artificially cripple it under &amp;ldquo;obsolete&amp;rdquo; Windows 7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO RUN NODE.JS 18.18 LTS ON OBSOLETE WINDOWS 7</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-run-latest-node-js-on-obsolete-windows-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-run-latest-node-js-on-obsolete-windows-7/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED ON: 2024-08-29&#xA;Node.js dropped Windows 7 &amp;ldquo;support&amp;rdquo; rigth after [version number 13].What a load of sh#t. Today i&amp;rsquo;ll tell you how to overcome this nonsense and run latest LTS version [Node.JS 18.x] without any problems. More newer versions may work also. I&amp;rsquo;ll leave you some room for experiments. Recently i found excellent already [patched installer of NodeJS 18]&#xA;First of all you need to download zipped version of software, not msi one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO RUN 16-BIT APPLICATIONS IN WINDOWS 7 X64</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-run-16-bit-applications-in-windows-7-x64/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-run-16-bit-applications-in-windows-7-x64/</guid>
      <description>As you may already know, there is no official ability to execute old 16-bit software in 64-bit operating systems. So if you have favorite Windows 3.x applications such stupid restriction was a complete bummer. But only until today! At least for me. WinVDM will resolve your frustration.&#xA;For providing such valuable information thanks goes out to [NeonFloppy website].&#xA;► WINVDM @ GITHUB&#xA;Unpack archive anywhere, execute INSTALL with admin privileges and you are good to go After installation working state could be checked by [Windows 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO FLASH ROOTED ANDROID 8 ON SONY XPERIA XZ1 COMPACT IN WINDOWS 7 ENVIRONMENT</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-flash-rooted-android-8-on-sony-xperia-xz1-compact-in-windows-7-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-flash-rooted-android-8-on-sony-xperia-xz1-compact-in-windows-7-environment/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED ON: 2023-04-20 Important update, substantial refactoring, many errors fixed&#xA;▒ PREFACE WORDS Following instruction is dedicated to flashing stock Android 8.0 firmware for Russian region, but almost all information can be applied to USA or any other region firmware. So, no restrictions here.&#xA;Remember that all commands and programs should be executed with admin privileges and your account must have administrator rights! If something goes wrong for some reason be sure to check [TROUBLESHOOTING] section!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO RUN OBS STUDIO V29 IN WINDOWS 7</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-run-obs-studio-29-in-windows-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-run-obs-studio-29-in-windows-7/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll keep post updated if any changes happen.&#xA;Recently last officially supported version was [27.4.2]. But from now on we can use actual version of software.&#xA;Here is small instruction list on how to make things rollin&amp;rsquo; under mighty Windows 7:&#xA;Obtain hacked [QT 6.3.1 DLLs for Windows 7] ||| [Mirror] [QT6 is not officially supported] Download [CFF Explorer][direct link] for basic resource hackery Obviously grab latest zipped archive [OBS Studio 29.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANONKONG&#39;S WINDOWS 7 USB 3 DRIVER FOR MODERN AMD PLATFORMS HAS BEEN UPDATED!</title>
      <link>/news/canonkong-windows-7-usb-3-0-driver-for-modern-platforms-has-been-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/canonkong-windows-7-usb-3-0-driver-for-modern-platforms-has-been-updated/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED ON: 2024-09-20 I will surely return to post to bring update on FINAL version of driver&#xA;[Canonkong] brings [ANOTHER BIG UPDATE] to the marvellous modern USB3 driver for [Windows 7].&#xA;Latest version: 2024-09-13 Supported chipsets: X370, X399, B450, X470, TRX40, A520, B550, PRO565, X570, B560, X670, WRX80 Recommended motherboards: MSI, Gigabyte Not recommended: Asus [works, but with some restrictions] Not working at all: Asrock&#xA;► **[USB3 DRIVER MOD] ► **[ASUS VERSION] ► **[ACPI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>44 THREADS XEON WORKSTATION AND 32 THREADS OPTERON SERVER RETRO BUILDS</title>
      <link>/news/44-threads-xeon-workstation-and-32-threads-opteron-server-retro-builds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/44-threads-xeon-workstation-and-32-threads-opteron-server-retro-builds/</guid>
      <description>&lt;br&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As you already know i fed up using &lt;a href=&#34;https://trackerninja.codeberg.page/post/my-daily-driver-rig-based-upon-ryzen-5950x-running-windows-7&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;[modern Ryzen/Radeon hardware]&lt;/a&gt; and decided to go a bit retro. Cheap Chinese clone mobos and second-hand high-performance cpu&amp;rsquo;s of previous generations induced me to rebuild my workstation and also fool around with Opteron-based server.&#xA;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Here is &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1qW1QraucVBm6pHzoD8yUvza9RhgzjQEJ0p78FHJifeY&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;[very detailed spreadsheet comparision]&lt;/a&gt; of almost all available Chinese x79/x89/x99 boards on the market.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 YEAR OLD MAN WHO CLIMBED OUT THE WINDOW AND DISAPPEARED [2013]</title>
      <link>/news/100-year-old-man-who-climbed-out-the-window-n-disappeared/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/100-year-old-man-who-climbed-out-the-window-n-disappeared/</guid>
      <description>&#xA;Delicate [Swedish humour] at its best.&#xA;MOVIE TRAILER Imagery by spacedrone808 @Adobe Imagery by spacedrone808 @Freepik </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAR MANAGER ▀ FASTEST TEXT FILE MANAGER FOR WINDOWS 7</title>
      <link>/news/far-manager-fastest-file-manager-for-windows-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/far-manager-fastest-file-manager-for-windows-7/</guid>
      <description>&#xA;Lightning fast text two-panel orthodox file manager with loads of functionality. These blue panels take very special place in my heart. Maybe because i&amp;rsquo;m using software right from the mid 90s. Still under active development. 64-bit version is preffered.&#xA;[DOWNLOAD FAR MANAGER]&#xA;Imagery by spacedrone808 @Adobe Imagery by spacedrone808 @Freepik </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO RUN AFFINITY PHOTO USING CLASSIC WINDOWS 7 INTERFACE WITHOUT AERO ENABLED</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-run-affinity-photo-using-classic-windows-7-interface-without-aero-enabled/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-run-affinity-photo-using-classic-windows-7-interface-without-aero-enabled/</guid>
      <description>&#xA;By default software forbids execution when you are using classic desktop and aero is not enabled.&#xA;However, there is a nice workaround. By adding &amp;ndash;no-dwm-warning switch to starting shortcut you can avoid internal restriction.&#xA;&amp;#34;C:\Program Files\Affinity\Photo\Photo.exe&amp;#34; --no-dwm-warning NOTE: with some graphical drivers you may experience visual artifacts and not so precise image rendering.&#xA;Imagery by spacedrone808 @Adobe Imagery by spacedrone808 @Freepik </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAN SONY XPERIA XZ1 COMPACT AND NOKIA PUREVIEW 808 HANDLE 1TB SD CARD?</title>
      <link>/news/can-sony-xperia-xz1-compact-and-nokia-pureview-808-handle-1tb-sd-card_/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/can-sony-xperia-xz1-compact-and-nokia-pureview-808-handle-1tb-sd-card_/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED ON: 2023-04-19&#xA;Most modern marketing smart-phones are mumbling about support of really large SD cards. But only on Hi-End models. I&amp;rsquo;m not even speaking about pathetic iphones, which are disabled in terms of external storage due to the greed of executive directors. In this note i will check old mastodonts like:&#xA;[Sony Xperia XZ1 Compact [2017]] [Nokia PureView 808 [2012]] for compatibility with such ENORMOUS storage device.&#xA;Sony XZ1 Compact handles such capacity without any problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FALLOUT I/II ▀ BEST RPG EVER!</title>
      <link>/news/fallout-1-2-best-rpg-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/fallout-1-2-best-rpg-ever/</guid>
      <description>My favorite game of all times. Thanks to it I’ve learn English [to some kind of degree] and even was almost expelled from university. What a neat memories. I was totally obsessed with deep &amp;ldquo;in game&amp;rdquo; atmosphere. Cyberpunk post-apocalyptic stuff, you know what I’m saying and those incredible ambient from master [Mark Morgan]. Can firmly confirm that modern series of this franchise don’t provide such immersion. As for backdrop music, Mark Morgan in Fallout ½ set quality bar to unreachable level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO REPAIR BROKEN WINDOWS 7</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-repair-broken-windows-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-repair-broken-windows-7/</guid>
      <description>To check system hard drive and fix errors:&#xA;chkdsk c: /f To check system hard drive, fix errors, locate and mark bad sectors:&#xA;chkdsk c: /r Very basic command to check integrity of system files:&#xA;sfc /scannow If sfc can&amp;rsquo;t help you try DISM.&#xA;Check system health for any corruption presence:&#xA;Dism /Online /Cleanup-Image /CheckHealth Check system health for store corruption presence:&#xA;Dism /Online /Cleanup-Image /ScanHealth Finally, repair command:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
