<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows 7 on Hugo Hacker Theme</title>
    <link>/categories/windows-7/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows 7 on Hugo Hacker Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/categories/windows-7/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1950X / 5950X / 7950X ▀ SUPER MEGA RETROSPECTIVE WINDOWS 7 BENCHMARK</title>
      <link>/news/1950x-5950x-7950x-super-mega-retrospective-windows-7-benchmark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/1950x-5950x-7950x-super-mega-retrospective-windows-7-benchmark/</guid>
      <description>¶ INTRO WORDS Numbers, numbers, numbers &amp;hellip; i say NUMBERS!!!!&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since i ran into the craze of pointless benchmarks. And now I&amp;rsquo;m back with the absolute procrastination stuff. Are you happy with this?&#xA;Take a note that 3DMark 03, 3DMark 05, 3DMark 06, 3DMark Vantage [2007], 3DMark 2011 and 3DMark 2021 are not marked by ▒ sign, showing the fact that these programs lost the soul of demoscene and just providing comparison numbers, nothing else.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO PRANK YOUR COLLEAGUE OR FRIEND WITH A PROFESSIONAL KEYBOARD FILTER</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-prank-your-colleague-or-friend-with-a-professional-keyboard-filter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-prank-your-colleague-or-friend-with-a-professional-keyboard-filter/</guid>
      <description>So you want to do something evil or make a present for the April&amp;rsquo;s Fool Day to your surrounding. Today we&amp;rsquo;re going to use the professional keyboard application [FilterKeys Setter] in its meanest form, will set keyboard filters to skip keystrokes, but only if the person starts typing at a faster rate.&#xA;I find out that the easiest way is to set Ignore Under parameter somewhere around 60ms, so it will be not so obvious in the beginning for the end user, that key strokes are skipping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO TRANSFORM APPALLING GUI OF WINDOWS 10 INTO WINDOWS 7 AWESOMENESS</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-transform-appalling-gui-of-windows-10-into-windows-7-awesomeness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-transform-appalling-gui-of-windows-10-into-windows-7-awesomeness/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED ON: 2024-11-12&#xA;Due to the fact that I was forced to use windows 10 at my primary work, I have to accumulate all these software to prevent myself from daily vomiting provoked by original windows 10 diarrhea.&#xA;Ok, kids, you don&amp;rsquo;t like the native looks of Windows 10? So am i! That is why today we transform atrocious Windows 10 interface into clean looking heaven of classic Windows 7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A QUICK NOTE ON THE RYZEN 7700 ADOPTION PROCESS</title>
      <link>/news/a-quick-note-on-the-ryzen-7700-adoption-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/a-quick-note-on-the-ryzen-7700-adoption-process/</guid>
      <description>Initially, I decided to install Windows Server 2008 R2, attracted by the opportunity to have a server-class operating system with increased I/O throughput in the works. But almost immediately i ran into compatibility problems [no surprise here] with my existing software. Some programs refuse to run because of artificial restrictions [you know licensing mambo-jambo stuff], some of which depend on components that are not present in Windows Server. It&amp;rsquo;s sort of possible to work, but you almost always run into little glitches here and there, even after converting it to a [workstation].</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAPSTER CONVENIENT WAY TO EXECUTE THINGS ON WINDOWS 7 STARTUP</title>
      <link>/news/capster-convenient-way-to-execute-things-on-windows-7-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/capster-convenient-way-to-execute-things-on-windows-7-startup/</guid>
      <description>Although I have been using Linux more and more in recent work, Windows 7 remains my main production operating system. And here is an excellent finding for Windows 7 crony named [Capster]. Its main functionality is to launch the specified executable at startup time when the [CAPS LOCK] key is set to ON or OFF. I use Capser to run backup script, that backs up previously selected folders [if i want to].</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO COPY FILES FROM ANDROID PHONE TO PC IN AN EASY AND FAST WAY</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-copy-files-from-android-phone-to-pc-in-an-easy-and-fast-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-copy-files-from-android-phone-to-pc-in-an-easy-and-fast-way/</guid>
      <description>First things first. I often need to copy substantial amount of photos from my phone. It can&amp;rsquo;t be done via Windows GUI without millions of mouse clicks or keystrokes. Here you will find a solution on how to do this in a proper way. The key tool for this will be [ADB], developer tools for Android.&#xA;Wishes: command line, batch, no file explorer, no mouse, no clickety-clack.&#xA;Sicking tired of all of these not-so-precise-instructions i&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make my own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO SETUP CUSTOM FONTS IN WINDOWS 7 CONSOLE</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-setup-custom-fonts-in-windows-7-console/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-setup-custom-fonts-in-windows-7-console/</guid>
      <description>As a hardcore user of [dual-panel orthodox file manager] i always suffered because of sucky look of default console fonts. Native preloaded font list has quite scarce selection, if you ask me. To fix such disappointment you&amp;rsquo;ll need:&#xA;install desired fonts by means of windows control panel copy EXACT FONT NAME fonts section in control panel paste it into registry key into following branch HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SOFTWARE\Microsoft\Windows NT\CurrentVersion\Console\TrueTypeFont note that every new subsequent font should be added by a key with added one zero to registry key name reboot computer to apply &amp;amp; enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO FIX &#34;UNABLE TO RENDER ERROR&#34; 0x80131501 IN VEGAS PRO 21</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-fix-unable-to-render-error-0x80131501-in-vegas-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-fix-unable-to-render-error-0x80131501-in-vegas-21/</guid>
      <description>Vegas video montage software is widely known as pretty glitchy application especially if we are speaking about latest versions. Newest Vegas 21 Pro is no exception. I run into problems almost instantly. Right after i&amp;rsquo;ve decided to render video clip. Upon export attempt application showed me error:&#xA;0x80131501 How typical! To fix things up i just took DLL library [RenderAsDialog.dll, which is responsible for export dialog] from previous Vegas Pro 18 [sub-version 284 to be precise] and substituted original file with above mentioned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO TRANSCRIBE AUDIO SPEECH INTO TEXT USING PYTHON</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-transcribe-audio-into-text-using-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-transcribe-audio-into-text-using-python/</guid>
      <description>Recently i was asked for a simple &amp;amp; free way of transcribing audio speech into plain text. Problem was solved via Python library called [Vosk]. It is a speech recognition toolkit working in offline environment.&#xA;To make things happen do the following:&#xA;[Install vosk] pip install vosk [Download speech model] of required language, larger libraries bring just marginal improvement over the smaller ones despite the fact that they are over 40 times bigger in a size.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO ENABLE SVG PREVIEW IN WINDOWS EXPLORER ON WINDOWS 7</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-enable-svg-preview-in-windows-explorer-on-windows-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-enable-svg-preview-in-windows-explorer-on-windows-7/</guid>
      <description>So, you want to be a hip and would like to have the feature of SVG preview in file explorer like in fancy windows 11 of friend of yours? It is surely possible, even on such old crone like Windows 7!&#xA;[SVG See] is an excellent application, which bring such functionality to our crony operating system.&#xA;If you are for some reason don&amp;rsquo;t observe SVG previews in explorer there are a couple of things that you could try to fix things up:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO FIX OUT OF SYNC TIME ON OLD WINDOWS 7 INSTALLATIONS</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-fix-out-of-sync-time-on-old-windows-7-installations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-fix-out-of-sync-time-on-old-windows-7-installations/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago i run into problem related to out-of sync time clock. Tried almost all imaginable solutions, like time service restarting, checking that internet time-sync option is turned on and so on and so forth. Of course to no avail at all. How typical! My Windows 7 installation dates back to early 2019 and i&amp;rsquo;ve plethora of software installed, and more over system is heavily customized so plain reinstall of operating system is not an option in my case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO COMPLETELY DISABLE TELEMETRY SERVICES WHICH DIAL BACK TO THIRD-PARTIES IN FIREFOX</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-completely-disable-telemetry-services-which-dial-back-to-third-parties-in-firefox/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-completely-disable-telemetry-services-which-dial-back-to-third-parties-in-firefox/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED ON: 2023-09-06 Some new parameters were added.&#xA;Note that by default all [Nightly versions] of Firefox are sending back telemetry to third-parties in extensive manner. So, to disable such malicious actions besides turning off telemetry settings via standard GUI options:&#xA;about:preferences#privacy You&amp;rsquo;ll need to use good old:&#xA;about:config To change to:&#xA;FALSE &amp;hellip;or create following parameters in software registry:&#xA;toolkit.telemetry.archive.enabled&#xD;toolkit.telemetry.enabled&#xD;toolkit.telemetry.unified&#xD;toolkit.telemetry.unifiedIsOptIn&#xD;toolkit.telemetry.bhrPing.enabled&#xD;toolkit.telemetry.firstShutdownPing.enabled&#xD;toolkit.telemetry.hybridContent.enabled&#xD;toolkit.telemetry.newProfilePing.enabled&#xD;toolkit.telemetry.reportingpolicy.firstRun toolkit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO STAY SAFE WHEN USING OB-SOUL-EEE-TEE WINDOWS 7 IN 2023?</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-stay-safe-when-using-ob-soul-eee-tee-windows-7-in-2023-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-stay-safe-when-using-ob-soul-eee-tee-windows-7-in-2023-/</guid>
      <description>I often get asked regarding Windows 7 safety especially in 2023.&#xA;&amp;#34;Is it safe to use such old operating system?&amp;#34; &amp;#34;What about security?&amp;#34; &amp;#34;How about modern viruses?&amp;#34;&#xD;.... &amp;hellip;. and many other similar questions.&#xA;Funny thing that people who are asking about security don&amp;rsquo;t give a damn about privacy. Yeah, that&amp;rsquo;s quite different definitions for sure, but from my point of view they always come together hand in hand.&#xA;The main and the most important security police officer is your head.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO MINIMIZE LAPTOP POWER CONSUMPTION</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-minimize-laptop-power-consumption/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-minimize-laptop-power-consumption/</guid>
      <description>Say you need to run on a laptop battery vintage or simply non-demanding applications for an extremely long time. Here is a little breakdown of mandatory things to do:&#xA;turn off in BIOS unneeded devices like camera, sd-card reader, fingerprint scanner, gsm-modem, wifi, bt or whatever you are not using turn on power saving features like various C-power states turn off hyper-threading and hi-core count [if you have such ability] lower screen brightness to acceptable level check my [quick] and [comprehensive] optimization FAQs get rid of [unneeded services and bloat applications] Also you can use core parking utility [Park Control], but in this mini-guide i&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to set power related things up via internal Windows 7 tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO SET PROPER COLOR FOR CURSOR AND COMMENTS IN VSCODE EDITOR</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-set-proper-cursor-color-in-vscode/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-set-proper-cursor-color-in-vscode/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED ON: 2023-12-02&#xA;The main reason i&amp;rsquo;ve decided to write this note is indistinct default color mappings and inability to solve issue simply using GUI of software.&#xA;In main configuration file:&#xA;settings.json add following lines:&#xA;&amp;#34;workbench.colorCustomizations&amp;#34;: {&#xD;&amp;#34;editorCursor.foreground&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;#ff0000&amp;#34;,&#xD;&amp;#34;terminalCursor.foreground&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;#02ED3D&amp;#34;,&#xD;&amp;#34;editorLineNumber.activeForeground&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;#ff0000&amp;#34;,&#xD;&amp;#34;editor.lineHighlightBackground&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;#016119&amp;#34;,&#xD;&amp;#34;editor.lineHighlightBorder&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;#02ED3D&amp;#34;,&#xD;&amp;#34;terminal.foreground&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;#02ed3d&amp;#34; }, To set custom color for GREY comments drop in these lines:&#xA;&amp;#34;editor.tokenColorCustomizations&amp;#34;: {&#xD;&amp;#34;conmments&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;#ff006f&amp;#34;&#xD;} To fast access configuration file press:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO RUN LATEST VS CODE IN WINDOWS 7 X64</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-run-latest-vs-code-in-windows-7-x64/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-run-latest-vs-code-in-windows-7-x64/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED ON: 2024-07-05 v1.81.1 is a more recent version, which can be executed without any efforts v1.89 is a hacked [FINAL version] for Windows 7 x64 So, Windows 7 users are pretty safe at this point despite artificial restrictions of big corps.&#xA;Usually i&amp;rsquo;m not feeling so delightful regarding microsoft modern programs, but this one is pretty good. And of course they tried to artificially cripple it under &amp;ldquo;obsolete&amp;rdquo; Windows 7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO RUN NODE.JS 18.18 LTS ON OBSOLETE WINDOWS 7</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-run-latest-node-js-on-obsolete-windows-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-run-latest-node-js-on-obsolete-windows-7/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED ON: 2024-08-29&#xA;Node.js dropped Windows 7 &amp;ldquo;support&amp;rdquo; rigth after [version number 13].What a load of sh#t. Today i&amp;rsquo;ll tell you how to overcome this nonsense and run latest LTS version [Node.JS 18.x] without any problems. More newer versions may work also. I&amp;rsquo;ll leave you some room for experiments. Recently i found excellent already [patched installer of NodeJS 18]&#xA;First of all you need to download zipped version of software, not msi one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO RUN 16-BIT APPLICATIONS IN WINDOWS 7 X64</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-run-16-bit-applications-in-windows-7-x64/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-run-16-bit-applications-in-windows-7-x64/</guid>
      <description>As you may already know, there is no official ability to execute old 16-bit software in 64-bit operating systems. So if you have favorite Windows 3.x applications such stupid restriction was a complete bummer. But only until today! At least for me. WinVDM will resolve your frustration.&#xA;For providing such valuable information thanks goes out to [NeonFloppy website].&#xA;► WINVDM @ GITHUB&#xA;Unpack archive anywhere, execute INSTALL with admin privileges and you are good to go After installation working state could be checked by [Windows 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO FLASH ROOTED ANDROID 8 ON SONY XPERIA XZ1 COMPACT IN WINDOWS 7 ENVIRONMENT</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-flash-rooted-android-8-on-sony-xperia-xz1-compact-in-windows-7-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-flash-rooted-android-8-on-sony-xperia-xz1-compact-in-windows-7-environment/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED ON: 2023-04-20 Important update, substantial refactoring, many errors fixed&#xA;▒ PREFACE WORDS Following instruction is dedicated to flashing stock Android 8.0 firmware for Russian region, but almost all information can be applied to USA or any other region firmware. So, no restrictions here.&#xA;Remember that all commands and programs should be executed with admin privileges and your account must have administrator rights! If something goes wrong for some reason be sure to check [TROUBLESHOOTING] section!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO RUN OBS STUDIO V29 IN WINDOWS 7</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-run-obs-studio-29-in-windows-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-run-obs-studio-29-in-windows-7/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll keep post updated if any changes happen.&#xA;Recently last officially supported version was [27.4.2]. But from now on we can use actual version of software.&#xA;Here is small instruction list on how to make things rollin&amp;rsquo; under mighty Windows 7:&#xA;Obtain hacked [QT 6.3.1 DLLs for Windows 7] ||| [Mirror] [QT6 is not officially supported] Download [CFF Explorer][direct link] for basic resource hackery Obviously grab latest zipped archive [OBS Studio 29.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW EPYC 256 THREAD CPU FINALLY REACH WINDOWS 7 CORE COUNT LIMITATION</title>
      <link>/news/256-thread-epyc-cpu-finally-reach-windows-7-core-count-limitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/256-thread-epyc-cpu-finally-reach-windows-7-core-count-limitation/</guid>
      <description>Most of you already know how AMD substitute in terms of cores/threads count intel&amp;rsquo;s pathetic&amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo;degenerative CPU evolution into revolution. Drastic changes were brought by [Ryzen] CPUs in consumer market in late 2017. [Threadripper] and [Epyc] lines were introduced later on [for workstation and server market respectively].&#xA;► [128 core / 256 thread Epyc Bergamo CPU]&#xA;It would be nice to see 256 threads in Windows 7 task manager, but i don&amp;rsquo;t think that it is possible due to lack of drivers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANONKONG&#39;S WINDOWS 7 USB 3 DRIVER FOR MODERN AMD PLATFORMS HAS BEEN UPDATED!</title>
      <link>/news/canonkong-windows-7-usb-3-0-driver-for-modern-platforms-has-been-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/canonkong-windows-7-usb-3-0-driver-for-modern-platforms-has-been-updated/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED ON: 2024-09-20 I will surely return to post to bring update on FINAL version of driver&#xA;[Canonkong] brings [ANOTHER BIG UPDATE] to the marvellous modern USB3 driver for [Windows 7].&#xA;Latest version: 2024-09-13 Supported chipsets: X370, X399, B450, X470, TRX40, A520, B550, PRO565, X570, B560, X670, WRX80 Recommended motherboards: MSI, Gigabyte Not recommended: Asus [works, but with some restrictions] Not working at all: Asrock&#xA;► **[USB3 DRIVER MOD] ► **[ASUS VERSION] ► **[ACPI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>64-CORES/128-THREADS THREADRIPPER 3995WX WORKSTATION GRADE CPU CONFIRMED TO WORK IN WINDOWS 7</title>
      <link>/news/64-core-128-thread-threadripper-3995wx-confirmed-to-work-in-windows-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/64-core-128-thread-threadripper-3995wx-confirmed-to-work-in-windows-7/</guid>
      <description>Well known Chinese driver modder [Canonkong] confirmed that [64-cores/128-threads Threadripper 3995WX] based upon sWRX8 chipset works flawlessly in Windows 7 environment. Considering the news it looks like that more recent [5995WX] will also work without any issues. So, we have plenty of headroom in terms of system performance. As for me, i have no need to switch to &amp;ldquo;recent operating systems&amp;rdquo; like Windows 10/11.&#xA;Here is brief [confirmation] from the WinRaid forum:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO DEPLATFORM YOURSELF, ESCAPE PROFILE BUBBLE AND STOP PERSONAL DATA LEAKAGE</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-deplatform-yourself-escape-profile-bubble-and-stop-persoanl-data-leakage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-deplatform-yourself-escape-profile-bubble-and-stop-persoanl-data-leakage/</guid>
      <description>Stop using mainstream operating systems like Windows 11/10/8.1, modern Linux, like Ubuntu or modern MacOS versions. On mobile Android 14/13/12/11/10/9/8.1 are prohibited because they use neural networks to profile your device and dial back to “home” to dump your personal data and preferences. iOS from very beginning was very phony platform.&#xA;My personal choices are Windows 7 for desktop and Android 8.0 for mobile. These two cover my digital needs fully, no restrictions whatsoever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAR MANAGER ▀ FASTEST TEXT FILE MANAGER FOR WINDOWS 7</title>
      <link>/news/far-manager-fastest-file-manager-for-windows-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/far-manager-fastest-file-manager-for-windows-7/</guid>
      <description>&#xA;Lightning fast text two-panel orthodox file manager with loads of functionality. These blue panels take very special place in my heart. Maybe because i&amp;rsquo;m using software right from the mid 90s. Still under active development. 64-bit version is preffered.&#xA;[DOWNLOAD FAR MANAGER]&#xA;Imagery by spacedrone808 @Adobe Imagery by spacedrone808 @Freepik </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1950X / 3100 / 5950X / RADEON VII / 6900XT ▀ WINDOWS 7 MEGA BENCHMARK</title>
      <link>/news/1950x-3100-5950x-radeon-vii-radeon-6900xt-windows-7-super-mega-benchmark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/1950x-3100-5950x-radeon-vii-radeon-6900xt-windows-7-super-mega-benchmark/</guid>
      <description>¶ PREFACE NOTE Finally i have won the battle with my laziness and forced myself to complete this so looooooooongish project. Enjoy!&#xA;PS: 3DMark 03, 3DMark 05, 3DMark 06, 3DMark Vantage [2007], 3DMark 2011 and 3DMark 2021 are not marked by ▒ sign, showing the fact that these programs lost the soul of demoscene and just providing comparison numbers, nothing else.&#xA;█ COMPUTER CONFIGURATIONS CPUs: Threadripper 1 1950X / Ryzen 9 5950X / Ryzen 3 3100 GPUs: Radeon VII 16Gb / Radeon 6900XT 16Gb GFX SETTINGS: 2560x1600 32Bit color [where possible], ULTRA+ settings, Anti-aliasing is turned OFF COMPUTER TESTBEDS: [1] ► Threadripper 1950X / Asrock Taichi X399M / 64Gb DDR4 2667@2800Mhz / Radeon VII 16Gb [2] ► Threadripper 1950X / Asrock Taichi X399M / 64Gb DDR4 2667@2800Mhz / Radeon 6900XT 16Gb [3] ► Ryzen 3 3100 @3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO RUN AFFINITY PHOTO USING CLASSIC WINDOWS 7 INTERFACE WITHOUT AERO ENABLED</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-run-affinity-photo-using-classic-windows-7-interface-without-aero-enabled/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-run-affinity-photo-using-classic-windows-7-interface-without-aero-enabled/</guid>
      <description>&#xA;By default software forbids execution when you are using classic desktop and aero is not enabled.&#xA;However, there is a nice workaround. By adding &amp;ndash;no-dwm-warning switch to starting shortcut you can avoid internal restriction.&#xA;&amp;#34;C:\Program Files\Affinity\Photo\Photo.exe&amp;#34; --no-dwm-warning NOTE: with some graphical drivers you may experience visual artifacts and not so precise image rendering.&#xA;Imagery by spacedrone808 @Adobe Imagery by spacedrone808 @Freepik </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FASTEST AMD-BASED CARDS FOR LEGACY WINDOWS 98/2000/XP/7</title>
      <link>/news/fastest-amd-based-cards-for-legacy-windows-98-2000-xp-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/fastest-amd-based-cards-for-legacy-windows-98-2000-xp-7/</guid>
      <description>Quick breakdown of the most powerful AMD-based cards for legacy operating systems.&#xA;[X850XT PE] ► WINDOWS 98 [official drivers]/ Omega drivers] [HD 3870 X 2] ► WINDOWS 2000 [official drivers] plus some INF tinkering, will review that one later on [HD 5970] ► WINDOWS 2000 [Blackwingcat hacks] [R9 270X] ► WINDOWS XP [official drivers] [6950XT] ► WINDOWS 7 [official drivers] ◄ currently rocking on that one under Windows 7 wing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO REMOVE ANNOYING CONFIRMATION WINDOW WHEN COPYING FILES FROM PUTER TO CELLPHONE OVER DUMB MTP PROTOCOL</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-remove-annoying-confirmation-window-when-copying-files-from-puter-to-cellphone-via-mtp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-remove-annoying-confirmation-window-when-copying-files-from-puter-to-cellphone-via-mtp/</guid>
      <description>Of course you run into situations when you would like to copy &amp;ldquo;non-standard&amp;rdquo; files to your Android smartphone and dumb MTP protocol showed up window like this one:&#xA;And this torture repeated after every new file type copied. Such imbecility can be removed by following command in admin console:&#xA;regsvr32 /u wpdshext.dll That&amp;rsquo;s all, limitation is gone.&#xA;Another hint, which potentially can help to overcome weird design of MTP protocol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO REPAIR BROKEN WINDOWS 7</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-repair-broken-windows-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-repair-broken-windows-7/</guid>
      <description>To check system hard drive and fix errors:&#xA;chkdsk c: /f To check system hard drive, fix errors, locate and mark bad sectors:&#xA;chkdsk c: /r Very basic command to check integrity of system files:&#xA;sfc /scannow If sfc can&amp;rsquo;t help you try DISM.&#xA;Check system health for any corruption presence:&#xA;Dism /Online /Cleanup-Image /CheckHealth Check system health for store corruption presence:&#xA;Dism /Online /Cleanup-Image /ScanHealth Finally, repair command:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
