<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fallout on Hugo Hacker Theme</title>
    <link>/tags/fallout/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fallout on Hugo Hacker Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/fallout/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO PLAY CLASSIC FALLOUT 2 TO GET THE MOST OUT OF IT IN 2023?</title>
      <link>/news/how-to-play-classic-fallout-2-to-get-the-most-out-of-it-in-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/how-to-play-classic-fallout-2-to-get-the-most-out-of-it-in-2023/</guid>
      <description>So you want to do a deep dive into the best RPG game of all time and don&amp;rsquo;t know how do it in a right way in 2023? You&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place, coz unlisted slacker knows precisely what you need to do in the first place.&#xA;Here is a breakdown list of what you need to do to run Fallout 2 buttery smooth:&#xA;grab original [Fallout 2] distribution from GOG [latest version 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FALLOUT ▀ VAULT13 [TBD]</title>
      <link>/news/fallout-vault-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/fallout-vault-13/</guid>
      <description>Is an ambitious project to replicate Fallout 1 world using Fallout 4 engine. Currently game in it’s early stage of development, but location of Shady Sands was already showcased to the public.&#xA;Developers intend to redo original voice-over because of copyright trademarks. Moreover they are trying to copy voice aesthetics as close as possible to original Fallout 1. Also you can already preview multiple soundtracks created by [Radiofloyd].&#xA;As for me, I really like what they are doing, despite the fact that I&amp;rsquo;m not fond of Fallout 3/4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FALLOUT I/II ▀ BEST RPG EVER!</title>
      <link>/news/fallout-1-2-best-rpg-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/news/fallout-1-2-best-rpg-ever/</guid>
      <description>My favorite game of all times. Thanks to it I’ve learn English [to some kind of degree] and even was almost expelled from university. What a neat memories. I was totally obsessed with deep &amp;ldquo;in game&amp;rdquo; atmosphere. Cyberpunk post-apocalyptic stuff, you know what I’m saying and those incredible ambient from master [Mark Morgan]. Can firmly confirm that modern series of this franchise don’t provide such immersion. As for backdrop music, Mark Morgan in Fallout ½ set quality bar to unreachable level.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
